

Ming-Yang Ho



ikaminyou@gmail.com

github.com/Kaminyou

in linkedin.com/in/kaminyou

+886 952792255

Summary -

A data scientist at aetherAI with 4+ years of experience in 2D/3D computer vision, natural language processing, machine learning, and deep learning algorithms development.

Besides, I am also adept at web programming, cryptography, and clinical pharmacy.

Skills -

- Programming related
 - Python
 - PyTorch
- •C/C++
- ReactJS
- MySQL
- Docker
- •Linux
- •Git
- Domain
 - •2D/3D computer vision
 - Natural language processing
 - Cyber security

Language -

- ·Mandarin (native)
- •English (TOEIC 825) [2014]
- Japanese (JEPT N1) [2021]

Interests

Machine learning, Deep learning, Full stack development, Cyber security

Work experience

Data Scientist

aetherAI, Oct. 2021 - (Current)

Teaching Assistance (TA)

NTU EE Machine Learning, Feb. 2021 - Jul. 2021

NTU EE Web Programming, Feb. 2021 - Jun. 2021

NTU CSIE Bioinformatics and Cheminformatics, Sep. 2020 - Jan. 2021

Data Engineer Intern

Dcard, Jun. 2020 - Dec. 2020

- •Built an automatic image cropping system to attract users' attention.
- •Invented a malicious applicants detection system with SimCLR.
- Established a system to immediately detect offensive comments.

Software Engineer Intern

Institute of Information Science, Academa Sinica, Jul. 2019 - Aug. 2019

•Leveraged the concept of RGB channels to assist in SNP prediction.

Honors

2021 PyCon APAC Speaker

Get 3D models out of nothing: Python implementation of deep learning-based 3D models reconstruction from 2D images..

2021 PyCon TW Speaker

Implementation of a deep learning-based saliency detection system by Python

2020 HITCON Speaker

Potential Security and Privacy Issues in Novel Taiwanese National eID system

Awards

2021 Outstanding Paper Award

2021 Multi-label Classification on CT Medical Imaging Competition, 3rd prize ICH detection enhanced by asymmetric loss with CNN-LSTM approach.

Recent Projects

2021 SUPERB: Speech processing Universal PERformance Benchmark

Entrusted by NTU, CMU, MIT, and Facebook AI to build a leaderboard web server for SUPERB Benchmark. (https://superbbenchmark.org/)

2021 Template is all you need: 2D to 3D reconstruction with template learned by contrastive learning

Developed a 2D to 3D reconstruction DL model leveraging the template concept.

Education

2019~2021 Master of Science (@CSIE CMDM) GPA 4.2 (Best thesis award)

Computer Science (bioinformatics specialization) *BEBI, National Taiwan University (NTU)*

Thosis

Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features

2014~2019 Doctor of Pharmacy GPA 4.1 (CS-related GPA: 4.3, Outstanding Graduate Award)

Clinical Pharmacy

School of Pharmacy, National Cheng Kung University (NCKU)

Publications

Ho, M. Y., et al. (2022) Ultra-high-resolution unpaired stain transformation via Kernelized Instance Normalization. [under review]

Liu, L. C., Ho, M. Y., Su, B. H., Wang, S. Y., Hsu, M. T., & Tseng, Y. J. (2021). PanGPCR: predictions for multiple targets, repurposing and side effects. *Bioinformatics*, 37(8), 1184-1186.

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) Look, Listen, and Diagnose: a deep learning based comprehensive Parkinson's disease evaluation system with 3D point cloud and acoustic features. [unpublished manuscript]

Ho, M. Y., Kuo, M. C., et al. (2022) *A 2D camera is all you need: gait analysis with frontal-view 2D video by deep learning-based 3D estimation.* [unpublished manuscript]